doityourselfrv.com 2017-12-13

# Privacy Policy | RV Mods - RV Guides - RV Tips | DoItYourselfRV

At DoItYourselfRV.com, the privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used. We will never share your email address or any other personal information to anyone without your direct consent.

### **Google Analytics**

Like millions of other website owners, we use [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) to track data about our visitors.

### **What does Google Analytics record?**

  * What website you came from to get here.
  * How long you stay for.
  * What kind of computer you’re using (iPad, PC, Mobile Phone, etc.)
  * And quite a bit more (How many articles did you read, your country/state of origin, etc)

### **What do we do with Google Analytics data?**

The tracking information allows us to better understand the kind of people who visit DoItYourselfRV.com and what content they’re reading. This allows us to make better decisions about design and writing. We can figure out what people like and try to build on that. Occasionally, we will compile aggregate statistics about the number of visitors this site receives and browsers being used. No personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting. Alternatively you can opt out of [Google’s advertising tracking cookie](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) or use their browser plugin to opt out of all [Google Analytics tracking.](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

###  **Log Files**

Like many other websites, we use log files to help learn about when, from where, and how often traffic flows to this site. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

### **Cookies and Web Beacons**

DoItYourselfRV may use cookies. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to a website.

### **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on DoItYourselfRV.com
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to DoItYourselfRV.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

### **Our Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies, javascript and web beacons on our site.

### Our advertising partners may include:

[Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) and [Amazon](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496), among others. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad companies for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. DoItYourselfRV.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### **Consent**

Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email by visiting our [About Us Page](http://www.doityourselfrv.com/about-us/)

_Last updated: May 23, 2015_
